<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<application name="dbtester" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://isis.astrogeology.usgs.gov/Schemas/Application/application.xsd">

  <brief>
    Outputs a PVL file that contains camera infomation. 
  </brief>

  <description>
    This program requires the user supply a "level 1" cube.  That is, a cube in raw camera geometry.
    The user can choose to run spiceinit on the input cube.  Spiceinit will use the system kernels,
    so any user updates to SPICE information will be lost.  The default is to <b>not</b> run spiceinit.
    This program will output various spacecraft and insrument related information.   Some of the
    output information will be a compilation of all bands, this will be put in the "Common" object of the 
    PVL.  Other infomation will be for a given band and placed in the "BandSet" object. the user
    can use the "output options" check boxes to control the infomation that will be output to the 
    PVL.  if the polygon option is chosen, the image polygon is output in well known text format.  
    The following is an example of  the output given when vimsdbgen is ran:
  </description>

  <history>
    <change name="Kris Becker" date="2010-06-07">
      Original version
    </change>
  </history>

  <category>
    <categoryItem>Database</categoryItem>
  </category>

  <groups>
    <group name="Files">
      <parameter name="FROM">
        <type>cube</type>
        <fileMode>input</fileMode>
        <internalDefault>None</internalDefault>
        <brief>
          Filename of a cube
        </brief>
        <description>
          This is the name of a single ISIS Cassini VIMS image cube that will be 
          added to database.  It is optional and useful for processing single 
          files, one at a time.  It is intended to be used to selectively 
          update cubes.
        </description>
        <filter>
          *.cub *.CUB
        </filter>
      </parameter>
      <parameter name="FROMLIST">
        <type>filename</type>
        <internalDefault>None</internalDefault>
        <fileMode>input</fileMode>
        <brief>
          Name of file containing list of Cassini VIMS ISIS cubes
        </brief>
        <description>
          This file contains a list of Cassini VIMS ISIS cube files that will be 
          processed and added to the database file.  It can be used in addition 
          to the FROM parameter.  
        </description>
        <filter>
          *.lis
        </filter>
      </parameter>
      <parameter name="PROFILE">
        <type>string</type>
        <default><item></item></default>
        <fileMode>input</fileMode>
        <brief>
          Specify the name of a specific database access profile
        </brief>
        <description>
          <p>
            This file is an existing VIMS pixel database that has been created by 
            a previous run of this application.  If provided, it will have all 
            processed input files added to it, first by searching for an existing 
            entry and replacing it with new data, or adding it to the database if 
            it does not already exist.
          </p>
          <p>
            If this file name is given, the CONFIG parameter will not be used as 
            the configuration parameters are stored in its label.
          </p>
        </description>
        <filter>
          *.pdb
        </filter>
      </parameter>
      <parameter name="DBTO">
        <type>filename</type>
        <fileMode>output</fileMode>
        <brief>
          output PVL filename
        </brief>
        <internalDefault>None</internalDefault>
        <description>
          A text file in label format (PVL) which will contain the results of this program.  This file can
          be used in conjunction with the 'getkey" program in order to pass the results to another
          program when developing scripts.
        </description>
        <filter>
          *.txt
        </filter>
      </parameter>
     <parameter name="CONFIG">
        <type>filename</type>
        <fileMode>input</fileMode>
        <brief>
          Input PVL file containing processing parameters
        </brief>
        <internalDefault>None</internalDefault>
        <description>
          This file contains parameters that will be used to specify or 
          constrain processing of input files.  The target, number of bands 
          expected/required, and geometric constraints will be used from this 
          file.
        </description>
        <filter>
          *.txt
        </filter>
      </parameter>
      <parameter name="ERRLOG">
        <type>filename</type>
        <fileMode>output</fileMode>
        <brief>
          Detailed output error summary
        </brief>
        <internalDefault>None</internalDefault>
        <description>
          This file will contain a detailed listing of errors that occured and 
          any specific error messages for each category of errors.  This can be 
          useful to get the description of the errors and individual specific 
          GIS GEOS exceptions.
        </description>
        <filter>
          *.log
        </filter>
      </parameter>
      </group>
   </groups>
</application>
